Welcome everyone to
the 5th Annual 2024
Gatorade "Supernova Sports Meet"
Together
Win once
So intense
Grab
Hold on, keep going
Come on
Hu Jiaxin is amazing
Beat the boys
So arrogant
It hurts so much
It really hurts
Hold on
Champion Zhang Jiayuan
First place girl
Fairy Girl Gen1es
Ruan Chijian Liuxing
Next up is
the 25-meter relay
This group is so fast
Ride the wind and waves forward
Cool, so cool
That girl is so fast
This group is a bit intense.
Zhang Weiwei crossed the line. Zhang Weiwei!
What is this?
What is this new move?
What did I just see?
My scalp is tingling.
Does he still have a spine?
Brother Wei
Don't cry, don't cry
Hello everyone, welcome to
the 5th Annual 2024
Gatorade "Supernova Sports Games"
Welcome
Next, we will have
the 25-meter shuttle run
This event mainly tests
the athletes' muscle explosiveness
and reaction ability
Let my coach introduce it
The first person proceeds
A round trip of twenty-five times two
Touch with your hand at the turnaround point.
After the door frame of the "Peacekeeper Elite" subway escape door
run back again
reach the finish line and high-five the second person
the second person continues the relay
a 25-meter round trip
after the same group touches the door frame twice
the door will open
after the second person returns to the finish line
the two people carry a ball back-to-back to the finish line
at the finish line
the "Peacekeeper Elite" subway escape door is set up
before the door completely closes
rush out of our subway escape door
calculate the total time
we will rank according to the total time
for ranking
Okay
Now let's give everyone some time
You can form teams freely
We need to try it out
You are the first runner, right?
Yes
You run first, come back
Then you run, come back
Then return
Leave some space on the back
We can't do it this way
This is a bit too tight
Then let's set a quick pace
Five, six, seven, eight
The steps have to be the same.
Then, whoever sees first runs.
The person who finishes running first gets the ball.
Wait there.
Then, place it here first.
And get ready.
Okay, okay.
Just the two of us back to back.
Hold the ball between us.
Let me think about the strategy.
We need to analyze this.
How do we analyze it?
Do you run fast?
You run fast.
I run too fast.
You run pretty fast, right?
I run okay.
When I turn around,
I'll hold the ball.
You just carry me directly.
That works.
I'll carry you.
Okay.
So next,
who wants to go first?
Come on, walk down directly.
Please.
Let's welcome Chen Muchi and Dan Jingyao.
Come here.
Why do you two want to go first?
Yes, we want to set an example.
Zuo and his partner are really strong.
Should we ask
if anyone wants to challenge them?
Yes, because looking at their build,
it seems like they have an advantage in this event.
they have a considerable advantage.
So I want to ask,
is there any team
willing to challenge them?
My brother Cong and my brother Fei
come
What do you think?
Bring in Chong.
It's just the two of us carrying it.
I flip it onto myself.
Holding the ball, "wham," it goes over.
"Wham," it goes over.
The first group is so dramatic.
The first group is setting an example for us.
The first group is showing us a new way to play.
Let's take a look.
Our two groups.
How will it turn out?
Go for it!
Three
Two
One
This door
Make sure to hold the ball tightly
Hold the ball tightly, don't drop it
Go
I flip it onto myself
Holding the ball, I quickly pass through
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen
Seven, eight, nine, ten
Fifteen, sixteen
Pay attention
The ball dropped halfway
Where did the ball drop
Please pick it up from where it dropped and hold it again
You need to return to the previous position
Return to the previous position
Although the door is already closed
We still hope both of you can finish the game
I just think
if Hexucong could find a good partner
his performance would be better
Sorry
Tactical failure
Complete tactical failure
I said
After the game, I said, Fei, your
your tactics don't work, your tactics
are completely just training me
to increase my intensity
How did Chen Muchi and Dan Jingyao feel just now
They were just thinking
to set an example for everyone
Not much of a feeling
How do you feel, Cong?
Mainly a bit heavy
Running further off course, running further off course
But Brother Zuo
when they were squeezing the ball
it actually gave a lot of inspiration to the following players
Yes
Because like Li Fei and He Xuchong
the height difference between them
is quite different
and it's easy to drop
the position of the squeeze is different
so everyone should consider the height
a bit more
This group seems quite strong
Are you confident?
Have you seen a sprint champion?
What's going on?
Anyway, I'm not
I didn't want to participate initially
but Mika grabbed my hand
and insisted we join together
so I had no choice
He is my best friend
So I definitely have to
Yes
Wait, let me ask
You just said Zando is your best friend
So you want to play with him, right?
Yes
Then between you and Zhou Keyu
and Zando, who is closer?
Let's get started.
Start, start.
Can you run slower?
I run very slowly.
I know.
That's why I chose you.
On your marks.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start quickly.
Not that, touch the door frame.
The door is already open.
Five, six, seven, go.
Come, come, come.
Left, right.
Wait a moment, pinch here.
This group is fast.
The ball dropped.
Move out a bit.
Yes, squeeze in the middle.
Come on
Open the door
I know you're home
What's wrong
Go in, go in
Come on, let's have the four of you back
So, as expected
Mika
It's different with your best friend
Yes, that's right
Thank you
Alright, thank you to both teams
Next up, the next group.
The girls' group is up next.
Over here,
Two boys and two girls form a team
Okay
I know Xu Mengjie is
the champion of past sprint races
a past champion
all
girls
are very formidable
It doesn't necessarily mean
you have to run with girls to win
Can you try running with boys
to stimulate your
potential abilities
Mengjie and I, both of us
want to challenge stronger
and more challenging things
Let me tell you
It seems like Chen Nanzhou is from Guangdong
the tennis champion
Yes
Tennis champion
is a professional athlete
Please take your positions
I really want to see this match
It's okay
Go for it
Just play casually
It's okay, it's okay
Don't be nervous
Don't fall
Come on
Three
Two
One
Basically the same
Mengjie
Xu Mengjie
Go Xu Mengjie
When we were halfway through the run,
we were both tied.
I won because my arms are longer.
I could touch the door frame earlier.
I could come back earlier, that's all.
This group is really fast.
Not slower than the men.
There's really not much difference.
Luckily, I didn't fall while running.
Really,
I would have lost face completely.
At the moment I got up,
I didn't think it was that serious.
It's okay, it's okay.
Xu Mengjie is a very strong person.
Yes, it looked quite painful.
A bit of a sting, prickly.
Luckily, there was no bleeding.
Looking over there,
two spots turned red.
Slow down, slow down.
Hold it, get ready to go.
Ball.
No good.
Didn't hold it properly.
Those two are not right.
I think everyone
who can participate in this project
definitely won't be too slow.
The most important thing is the soccer ball.
It will be very difficult.
Luckily, it didn't fall.
See? She didn't hold it properly with both hands.
Right.
I saw them holding the ball.
Alright, let's go.
Make sure to place the ball a bit higher.
Otherwise, it will easily fall.
Then hold it straight with your back.
Make sure not to stick your butt out.
Then walk with your back straight like this.
Fly.
We still have a strategy for grabbing that ball.
She first holds it like this.
Then I take it from her hand.
Like this, I pass it through.
The two of us hook it together.
Then we move forward.
Very good.
One, two.
Brother Zuo
You and I each use one hand now
in George's pocket
Feel around and see what you can find
Three, two, one
Nothing much, just swipe for a while
Bangs
He is carrying a Nezha.
Impressive, impressive.
Holding the ball with your neck is really impressive.
One, two, three.
Come on, TangoZ Zhongqi.
Hurry up, come on.
You too, come on.
He Wenjun.
Did you put the ball in your clothes?
I didn't touch it with my hands.
You know how to play.
So you triggered it.
A big reward of ten seconds deduction.
Next is
why we chose each other
because we have a good relationship
Yes
We still need to find an opponent
Where is Pinlin
Pinlin
Let's compete together
The four of us will compete together, right?
Okay
Aren't you tired of playing together every day?
A little.
Sometimes I play with others too.
But eventually, we always come back to each other.
It's still us playing together.
Are you confident?
In each other's performance?
Because I just asked around.
Actually, everyone is unsure about their own
performance; it's a mystery.
They don't know if they're fast or slow.
Okay.
Yes.
It's just running.
No problem with holding the ball.
It's hard to say.
Hard to say.
Let's take a look.
Because you four are very familiar with each other.
So we need to see how you four
perform in this round.
We'll review it later, okay?
Come on, let's have the four of you.
Come on, take your positions.
Three.
Two.
One.
Keep it up
Go for it!
Keep going
It's hard to say
When Li Quanzhe was running
his hair was flying
it flew straight back
The last time I saw hair standing straight
was after my mom took a bath
and it froze in the winter in the northeast
so quickly
Come on, come on
Careful, careful
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven
This one is fast
Eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve
This group is fast
This one is fast, this one is really fast
This group is really fast
Okay, okay
This group is fast
So fast
This group seems to be
Looking faster now, right?
Come on, how is it?
How does it feel?
"Backstab"
I kept asking him just now
I said let's speak from the heart
Are you really fast or not?
He said
Not fast
No, no, I haven't run in a long time either
I didn't expect it to be like this
But your group so far
is very, very fast
Just very fast
So let's look forward to the final results
Let's see if you perform well
Alright?
Okay, thank you, thank you
Come on, come on
Our little chick team
Your heights match well
No
When we were warming up backstage
Two girls looked at us
Come, take your positions.
Help me lift it together, lift together.
Come on, come on!
We already have male fans.
Who else will cheer for us?
Over here.
Fei, give it to Fei.
Give it to me, I'll do it.
Everyone, get ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Ride the wind and waves, charge forward
The fairy girl climbs the peak
So lucky
We won this battle
We won
Brother Fei
Why do you act like their boss?
What's wrong, Fei?
Fei, what's wrong?
Why are you so happy?
Mr. Li, please speak.
No, it's just the atmosphere.
May I ask you,
when you cheer for the Fairy Girls Gen1es,
which side is the Fairy Girls Gen1es on?
This side.
Of course, I know.
It's this side.
Come on, tell me, Li Fei.
What's her name?
Isn't it written here?
Read it out, Li Fei.
Fairy Girl Gen1es
How do you pronounce her name?
Ruan Chijian Liu
Yes
Right?
What about her?
Yean Chen
Why am I attracted to them
is because I think they are all amazing
just from these past two days of comparison
every project is impressive
including when you look at the
rankings
almost all of them
in every project
they took the top spots
I really think
they are an amazing group of girls
Gen1es
follow me
Li Fei
Brother Li Fei
thank you
Happiness came a bit too suddenly.
Broadcast that segment.
Song Muzi and He Wenjun just
jumped right on the spot.
They'll be "jealous" to death of me.
Okay.
That's it for now.
Does it sound good? Does it sound good?
Brother Li Fei
Alright, next group.
Fairy Girl Gen1es
One two, one two
Feige, who are you doing this for this time?
Thank you
It's still them
Is there anyone who hasn't run away?
Only you two are left.
Are there any boys who haven't run?
Sun Yue, Sun Yue is alone.
No teammates.
I won't run.
Sun Yue has no teammates.
No one else.
You go.
I can't.
Go, brother.
You come, Weiwei.
Did you not run?
I really can't do this.
Run, come on.
Since we're here.
Don't pull me, bro.
Regarding running,
I personally resist it a lot.
Not self-deprecating,
Seriously, it's just that your legs are long.
For the same distance, others take five steps.
You need to take seven or eight steps.
You're destined to not outrun them.
Actually, I never thought of trying.
But Sun Yue kept inviting me.
And then, indeed,
everyone had run.
So, let's do it.
Brother Wei,
I'll cheer for you.
Hurry up.
Brother Wei, Brother Wei.
We are very popular
What are you afraid of
Li Fei, are you calling Gen1es the fairy girl or
Just watch me perform
Go, Wei
Wei, you're the best
Wei
Come
Keke, you two are partners
because you were already teammates
so you have great chemistry
Yes, because we are about the same height
and
we have a good relationship
So, how do you evaluate your opponents?
Hello
How did you form a team?
They formed a team temporarily
Okay
I didn't expect the last group to be so exciting
Come, the four of you, please take your positions
Not so far, bro
Come, are you ready?
Ready
Three
Two
One
Keep going
Oulizhu PAILIU, keep going
I, Zhang Weiwei
am very honored
Just watch me perform
Wei Ge
Wei Ge, I can catch up
I can catch up
Wei Ge
Hurry, hurry
Sun Yue, go for it
Sun Yue
Charge
Go for it
There's still time, there's still time
Go for it, "Bossy CEO," go for it
One, two, three
One, one, one
Wei Ge, Wei Ge, Wei Ge
Wei Ge, go for it
Go for it
Wei Ge
Let them go first
Thank you, brothers and sisters.
Thank you all.
Thanks.
Just now, Oulizhu PAILIU ran very fast.
Did you capture it with your phone?
I didn't know you could run and film at the same time.
I wonder how the footage turned out.
Let's see.
Take a look.
Your footage is very good and clear.
So steady.
Brother Wei, Brother Wei
Brother Wei, you look so handsome
Waiting for you to take over, Brother Wei
Waiting for you to take over
Brother Wei, you look so handsome
Come on, let's check on him first
How are you, Brother Wei? Brother Wei
Are you okay?
My bad, my bad
I got it
Sun Yue
How are you today?
I fell twice.
But I tried hard.
Because it really is
for the sake of this team, right?
Since we joined, we have to take it seriously.
Yes, we can say that on the surface.
But actually, I think the two girls over there
If I do that again, it would be too embarrassing.
But I did it.
Once you get up there,
you don't want to stop.
Just me,
refusing is refusing.
If I don't go up, I don't go up.
But once I'm up there,
halfway through the run,
I don't want to stop.
And when I fell,
I could see Sun Yue
waiting for me on the other side.
Brother Wei,
he's waiting to take over my shift.
He needs to continue and finish.
No matter what, I
still have to get up and run.
Brother Wei, I can catch up.
Even though
in the end,
it's very slow,
and clumsy, stumbling,
I still
tagged Sun Yue,
and handed it over to him.
Come
I want to say something
Just now, we
actually arrived at almost the same time
at that doorway
but because the door was about to close
and then
if we went together, we would bump into each other
then
the two teachers said to let the girls go first
Brother Wei
let them go first
Yes, and then I heard it and then
Don't cry, don't cry
It was really touching, just
Yes, at that moment, I felt warm and touched
Yes, I can see that
Both teachers still
take great care of the girls, right?
I'm sorry
I saw you fall, I couldn't help you
Don't worry about it
because I fell myself
So I
Thank you, thank you, Group Two
Thank you
Brother Wei, you go handle that over there
Brother Wei, over there
You go directly to the back, over there
Actually, among us guys,
when he falls, the first feeling
isn't sympathy, it's to laugh.
Then later, we realize
that it was a real fall.
At that moment, we definitely feel sympathy.
Alright, everyone,
next, the ranking for this project
has been compiled.
Next,
we will announce
the rankings for this project.
First, we will announce
the third place.
Let's have Mr. Liao Bo announce it.
The third place
with a time of 30.72 seconds
So fast!
Let's congratulate Zando and Mika.
Did you ever think you would come in third place?
I really didn't think so.
But I'm quite happy.
What's next?
We are going to announce
the champion and the runner-up.
Their scores are very close.
Only a fraction of a second apart.
Let's welcome
Chen Muchi
Dan Jingyao to step forward
Next, let's welcome
Li Xikan and Li Quanzhe
Alright, next I will announce the results.
Chen Muchi, Dan Jingyao
Your time is
thirty seconds and twelve milliseconds.
Li Quanzhe, Li Xikan
Your time is
twenty-nine point fifty-three seconds
When the second and third places were announced
we didn't expect to get first place
nor did we expect ourselves to
we could achieve it
It seems
we didn't run well
I think
it's not surprising
there was a small mistake
when holding the ball
then there might have been a slight
pause
Hold the ball tight, hold the ball tight
Wait, wait
Not yet, not yet
Okay
We shouldn't stop with him.
We should be able to walk with him.
And guide him to that position.
In this way,
we might be able to save some more time.
It's possible, we might be able to reach that
first place.
Yes.
No matter who is first now,
who is second,
or who is third,
you are all strong competitors in this project.
So,
the six of you
will advance to the next round of
the "Peace Elite" advanced stage.
Do you want to see it?
Yes, I do.
I think Chandlerpan wants to see it the most.
Right, Chandlerpan?
Let's go together.
Next, we will announce
the detailed rules of the advanced competition.
This round will increase the difficulty of the assessment.
Athletes participating in this event
will be grouped in pairs.
They will perform a 25-meter back-and-forth run.
At the turning point, there will be
a level 7 pack from the "Peace Elite" subway escape mode.
The approximate weight is
12 kilograms.
24 jin.
It's quite heavy.
Competitors must carry the level 7 pack
to start the weighted run.
and continue the rest of the course.
And before our
"Peace Elite" subway escape door closes,
they must reach the designated escape point
to successfully complete the escape mission.
Let's see how you six want to choose.
Will you choose each other,
or choose someone else?
Then it's the two of us.
Each other or someone else?
It's fine, I'll face him.
Okay.
Then it's still the same.
It's still the two of us together.
Okay, let's go.
Teammates turning into opponents.
Yes.
Come on.
To be honest,
the weight of this bag
is not very friendly
to our group.
It feels like the two of them
are not as heavy as that bag.
Right?
Are you ready?
Three
Two
One
It's really heavy.
It's indeed a bit of a struggle.
Are you okay?
It feels heavy.
Like carrying a little person.
Very heavy.
Once you pick it up,
you'll feel like this.
When you carry the backpack,
when the backpack is on your back,
you'll feel like this.
I really think
it's completely unfriendly to me.
When I swing it,
I stumbled.
And even running,
I feel a bit strained.
Which team is up next?
The two of us.
You two, come on.
Are you ready?
On your marks,
three, two, one.
Come on, come on, come on
Handsome, so handsome.
Excellent
As expected, the best of friends.
So heavy.
Zando must have had a lot of fun.
It was okay.
Very tired.
Carrying it was okay.
Running with it is very heavy.
Next, let's have our final group take their positions.
Good luck.
Chen Muchi is my strongest opponent.
Because when we train,
we often go
to compete.
He was our number one or two back then.
I have also
known him for quite a while.
He is both a brother and a rival.
Also, I want to see
his growth.
Come on, everyone to your positions.
Three
Two
One
Come on, come on
Look how fast you ran.
Great job, great job.
Impressive, impressive.
You did it.
You're even faster than before.
Well done.
Actually, you can really feel that all six of you
are amazing.
Not only individually,
but also when running,
and even when carrying weights,
you are all very powerful.
Let's give another round of applause to the six of them.
Alright, the assessment for this project
is temporarily concluded.
We will now move on to today's
next event.
Next, we will have the flexibility pole race.
This event mainly tests
the athletes' muscle flexibility
and overall ligament flexibility.
Those who excel in this event
are suitable for live-streaming events like
rhythmic gymnastics and street dance.
Next, I will announce
our detailed rules.
One team is for the competition
I choose Xu Yizhen
Those who want to be the first to fight
please come and stand next to me.
I choose Xu Yizhen
I can't hold back anymore
Come on
Alright, go ahead, bye
I can't hold back anymore
So who do you choose?
Good luck
Please choose an opponent
Xuan Lu, come on
Come on, let's welcome Xuan Lu
We agreed on this
That's it
Are you going?
Yes, I'm going
Go ahead
Come on, let's welcome both of you, please take your positions
Three
Two
One
So difficult
The second one is very hard
I found the trick.
Quick, give up your seat.
No
Don't lose strength, don't laugh
Keep going
Slow down
It's okay
Keep going
It's too difficult.
Keep going.
It feels so bittersweet.
The forward roll was almost
This mental state
So much effort
This must be the spirit of sports
Both funny and bittersweet
And then it makes people feel
that
she has this confidence
and the effort to try
still
actually quite good
Yes, before I was actually resistant to some unfamiliar
projects or environments
I would avoid them, but now I feel okay
Participation is important, happiness matters
I saw Xu Yizhen
Do you know many states of the future?
Many states of the future in life
I will take good care of myself
Once it's over, it's great, right?
Yes
Let's give them a round of applause
Next group, come on.
He is very tall.
The two tallest people.
Are they going to hurdle?
No, He Xuchong...
Even if he bends three times, he can't get through.
The two of us are...
Let's test our waist strength and see.
See, tall people can actually get through.
A height group of 190 and 188.
The two of them...
Do they look like they're here for this competition?
That bar...
For people as tall as us...
It's a huge challenge.
But...
We want to prove one thing.
Tall people can also get through.
Three.
Two.
One.
Slow down.
Slow down the quality.
Go for it!
He's pretty impressive.
This is too low.
You can't even get through this on your knees.
No, no.
I think they are actually just
performing a ceremony
Chen Muchi "Father King"
"Father King"
How about we go over it first?
Let's give it a try.
How do we get through this?
The two of them
Wait a moment
Even tall people can squeeze through.
But they have to use a tall person's method to get through.
We should use our own method to get through.
Are you all reporting this?
Try it.
This Zhang Weiwei will definitely report it.
Yes, I just walk over normally.
I just hop over.
What is this?
Go Zhang Weiwei!
You are the best!
You two
Are you afraid of this competition
or is there some misunderstanding?
Yes, I want to see if we can unlock a new one.
way to pass.
Do they need to hold hands to get through?
Former partners
are ready to support each other.
Yes, that's right.
What is this new move?
You need to bend back, Zijie.
You need to bend back.
It's already come to this.
"Snap," he knelt down.
Has Zijie been praying for rain all this time?
Is your heart that sincere?
Can the post-production teacher add some music?
Put your hand in front like this.
Can't support anymore
Former partners are ready to support each other
His method is good.
Xiaobai's method is good.
Yes.
Very good.
For so many boys,
flexibility is too rigid.
There is no flexibility to speak of.
Let's clarify again.
The rules of the hurdle race.
Both knees touching the ground.
Any single point of the body touching the ground.
All are fouls.
Crawling directly is not allowed.
Hurdling is even more not allowed.
Li Fei, Li Fei
Break the spine
The last shot was indeed too low.
It couldn't go any lower.
It was much lower than I imagined.
This show is too brutal.
I thought it would be hard, but not this hard.
This might indeed be my breaking point.
Maybe I just didn't grasp the trick at that time.
That pole is too low.
And I can only go down.
It's not that smooth when I move.
It's still quite difficult.
Actually, it's not as hard as imagined.
It might be a bit harder for boys.
It might be easier for girls.
Who's next?
Wang Ke.
Come on.
Who do you want to choose?
I'll choose someone about my height.
Public height is 167 cm, anyone?
Okay, that's me, I'm 167 cm.
Hu Jiaxin, your public height is 167 cm.
168 cm, actual height is 167 cm.
Let me see.
Close enough.
Did you know each other before?
Yes.
My best friend.
I know her too.
We are also good friends.
Come and make your best friend proud.
How about we warm up first?
We've been sitting for too long.
Sure.
Alright.
Let's warm up.
Go for it!
Everyone, go for it!
Wang Ke
This appearance
Alright, no need to compete anymore
You've already passed
I declare you've already passed
Quick, give them an award
Come on, you two
Wait a moment
Warmed up and tired
A bit dizzy
It's okay, take a break
Alright
Three
Two
One
What happened?
I hit that pole right away.
That hit actually stunned me.
My waist actually lacks a bit of strength.
I kept my head down, hanging upside down.
I couldn't stand up.
So I hit it.
Wang Ke, Wang Ke, keep going!
Yes, yes, yes.
Two in a row
Three in a row
Oh my
A duel of experts
Both reached the shortest pole at the same time
What did I just see?
My scalp is tingling.
Her folding angle is like this.
Hello
I just went over the bar
It hurts so much
My back now
You look super flexible
You went over so easily
When I have free time
I practice Pilates and stuff
I also practice Pilates
But why am I so stiff
No worries, I'll teach you
You'll teach me
Yes
Can we exchange contact information
We can practice together in the future
Sure
Finally, I can add a beautiful girl
Come, let's get close
It's a deal, I'll guide you
Next time, I want to be like you
Just like this
Trust me
Let's go
Why are you two always tied together
Who chose whom
Mutual choice
Yes, mutual choice
Because
we are evenly matched opponents
Exactly
competing gives a special sense of rivalry
It's entertaining
Yes, equally tough
Are you ready?
Go for it!
Three, two, one
Slow down
Twins
So fast
A real match
Sure
Mutual "backstabbing"
Yes, this speed is quite fast
This group is a bit tense
You can see it out of the corner of your eye when passing the pole
He is especially fast
He actually motivates me
Yes, the faster he is, the faster I need to be
Help between opponents is also significant
The next one who wants to step forward
Didi, Ouyang Didi
Who do you want to choose?
Okay, then Sister Zhao Yue raised her hand
Okay
Both of you are about the same height
It seems so
Senior
As soon as we sat down today
Zhu Yimeng was saying
Wang Ke wants to meet Zhao Yue
And then, as the "social butterfly" of the team
I thought, of course, I want to
help my teammate get to know her
It was also mentioned yesterday
that Didi is very brave
and she reacts very quickly
and I really want to team up with her
Thank you
Senior and junior relationship
Actually, I'm looking forward to this group
What about you?
Good luck
Alright, this is a strong opponent
Didi is amazing
Oh my god
Record
To break the record
Didi walks very fast
Just like that, she went past alone
This is amazing.
This is terrifying.
Never got up.
This is her greatest strength.
She looks while pressing down.
Very smart, she bends her waist.
Then she turns her head to the side to look at the road.
Very fast.
Very excellent.
Didi's waist is very flexible.
Core strength is very strong.
She knows how to use it well during competitions.
Skills and strategies.
Really amazing.
The next one who wants to step forward
Come on, come on
Three, two, one
Go for it
You can do it
Very standard
The teacher mentioned the backbend
These are the competition rules
Just try to follow the competition rules as much as possible
This is too low
Keep it up
I also want to use it
Speed and quality should meet the standards
But maybe the speed
Anyway, just ensure one first
First, ensure the quality
Cool
Textbook
Just follow this standard
So impressive
So soft
She is so soft
So strong
I was just watching Sister Jiang Zhenyu
Her waist just hung there and she went through
Her waist is good, she was in a hanging state
She was using her waist strength
I was just offstage
Watching and feeling very confused
Jiang Zhenyu
I think she is
a very soft and delicate girl
but when it comes to competition
she is very cool
unbelievable
Actually, this sport
tests more than just flexibility
but also the strength of the waist and legs
as well as coordination and teamwork skills
She even stayed there for a while.
After the first few were done,
I felt it was hard to keep going
until the very last one.
Because the last one was really too low.
So I thought I shouldn't rush.
I had to go a bit slower.
So graceful
I also admire everyone's sportsmanship
Whether they succeed or not
No matter how many times they fall
Everyone still follows the rules
And tries their best to complete it
I find it really touching
I think the girls are giving their all
Keep it up
I think we really should
Give them a round of applause
Flexibility is not my strong suit
But I feel I need to
Give it my all
And strive for it
I don't think I'm flexible enough
But challenging myself
And overcoming myself
Is the most satisfying
Is there anyone who hasn't participated yet? Next group
Zhu Yimeng
She's really amazing
I just saw her demonstrate
She placed her hand there
Zhu Yimeng seems to look
very confident
Okay, I think it's fine
Who do you want to choose
Does anyone want to come
Zando
No
Zando wants to go
I don't want to go
Can we choose Teacher Zando
Yes, yes
First, this activity
is better suited for those good at street dance
is better
Others, just kidding
Go
Alright
Senior
I want to say something
The teacher just said this is street dance, right
Yes
There are no such moves in street dance
Really, there are no such moves in street dance
Do you want to open your own dance video
It's full of these moves
Give it a try
Put in some effort, give it a try
Please, both of you, take your positions
Go Yimeng
Go for it
Great job
Three
Two
One
Does she have a spine?
Just walk like this.
The praise is too high, it's a disadvantage.
Your own dance videos
are full of these kinds of moves.
Keep going
So impressive
This sport
A race of speed
In terms of speed
Non-standard is faster
Then I guess I'm more standard
Didn't you say this move isn't in street dance?
Alright, this project
The rankings have been compiled
I'll announce
the top two in the boys' group
With a time of 19.22 seconds
The second place goes to
Zando
Congratulations
Chandlerpan, yes
The first place with a time of 13.82 seconds
Much faster than me
Very stiff waist
I'll stand up.
Is it yours?
Congratulations, Liu Jiayi.
I think my backbend
might have some talent
I'll just give it a try
Just persevere, that's the sports spirit
You can stick with it
That's why you'll achieve results
Need speed
Must keep up with Crystal Pure
Freshly delivered, fresh for 21 days
Second place in the girls' group with a time of 11.69 seconds
Let's congratulate
Ouyang Didi
First place
Time: 10.85 seconds
Zhu Yimeng
Congratulations to Zhu Yimeng
Both are theirs
Cheers
I'm very happy that our Gen1es girls
won first and second place
Yes
Thank you, and then
we should be the
two youngest here
so let's keep it up
keep working hard
and learn from the older girls
Go for it
Yes
Next, we will start
the advanced competition
the designated moves pole competition
will include
bridge backbend
and side splits
Using methods like splits
to challenge the bar
Who wants to come?
Pinlin, Pinlin
It's my turn again, right?
It's your turn, right?
I can't, I can't
This really won't work
Go, Little Rainbow, go!
You really want to challenge yourself
I also hope that
I want to see if I can do it
See if I can inspire
my potential abilities
Yes
Go, go, go
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes
Okay, done
You can lower your head and go down slowly
Alright, the second challenge is the vertical split.
This is really...
That's too low.
You can do it, keep going!
Side split.
Keep going!
Quack
Yes, yes
Press it, press it
I challenged myself
Great, really great
Next, please
Ouyang Didi
I think she will be even prettier
Of course, the first one was also very pretty
They are all very pretty
This is
a standard demonstration
that stands out
as unique
Still manageable
So low
It's like a game
So impressive, so impressive
This is easier for them
Very easy
Sister Meng
Look, just a small test
Come on, let's start
Is it this soft?
Do they even have bones?
Yes
Okay, okay
Okay
It's done
The previous moves
We can get through with some core strength
This part relies purely on flexibility
So impressive
Impressive
Sports prodigy
Baby
Can all girls do it?
Very smooth
Jiang Zhenyu's overall state
feels like she has no bones
she passed through very smoothly
Very visually appealing
Aesthetic
Watching them play this
it seems like this activity isn't difficult
You know
it's very easy for them
Swam over
Have they all practiced gymnastics?
Many of these girls sing and dance
Most of the girls have a dance background
Unstoppable, unstoppable, unstoppable
Are there any professional players today?
Aren't they all professional players?
Originally, rhythmic gymnastics
doesn't have much to do with men
Can you do a backbend?
I don't think I can
I can
Come, I'll support you here, give it a try
Does this count?
Because you need to think about this action.
How will you continue moving forward?
Sustainability.
I don't plan to leave.
I'm just trying to see if it works.
Like this.
Then.
I can't do it.
Relax and move your hand back.
I'll catch your arm.
Come back.
You come.
Come on, why aren't you coming?
Come on, did the boy Li Quanzhe raise his hand?
Let's go
Let go
Why do you want to go, buddy?
Come on, come on
I regret it.
Head first.
Bring the legs back first.
Sure
I want to see if there are other guys
to challenge again
No way
This guy can actually go over there too
if he learns magic
and takes his head off
The honor of the boys depends on you.
Wu Zhengrong
Come
No problem
No problem at all
I see this
He is the only boy who signed up for gymnastics
I got goosebumps.
Because I study dance
I have this confidence
So I wanted to show myself
Alright, athletes
Next, we will move on to
Our next project competition today
We need to invite Coach Lang
Come and introduce it to us.
Next, we will proceed with
the battle rope challenge.
This event mainly tests the athletes'
overall muscle strength and endurance.
core strength's explosiveness and stamina.
Athletes participating in this event
are divided into men's and women's groups.
Each group consists of two people.
They will swing the battle ropes with both hands
and push the dumbbells
from the starting point to the designated endpoint.
The time limit is forty seconds.
If they cross the line within forty seconds,
the score will be calculated based on the time.
If they do not cross the line,
there will be no score.
It is important to note that
the position of the person
must not exceed the starting line.
If the dumbbell detaches from the battle rope,
the athlete should automatically return it to position
and continue the timed competition.
This is really difficult.
It's not about brute force, right?
No.
If you use brute force, you'll just lift it up.
Pushing it over won't work either.
Alright, let's give a warm round of applause
to welcome our superstar instructor Wu Zun
to give us a demonstration.
Feeling
Feeling so heavy
Three
Two
One
Is it this heavy?
It gets harder as you go.
It's already difficult here.
I feel so tired.
Keep going
Crossed the line
It requires skill.
If you can't find the technique,
you will be very, very tired.
Because you'll be swinging continuously.
Yes, and your arms will get very sore.
The timing of exertion is very important.
It can't be too intense either.
This is challenging.
For your entire body,
strength, balance, and endurance,
the demands are high.
I've tried this battle rope,
but never with dumbbells on it.
It seems a bit difficult for me.
When we usually work out,
fifteen kilograms for us
is a relatively normal upper weight.
a weight.
And then we have to take that rope
and push it forward.
It might be quite strenuous for me.
Alright, so next,
those who want to participate in this round, step forward.
Aren't you going?
Yes, I am.
Please, step forward.
Good luck.
Let's go.
I don't want to go up
You made me swing the battle ropes for thirty seconds
Not to mention thirty seconds
After ten seconds, I was seeing stars
I've been swinging them for about three months
Even now, it still hurts when I do this move
Right now
Go
Not going
Who pushes like this?
With coaxing and deception
Really impressive
Do you know why you need to participate in this?
Because no one has the skills
Everyone is studying this skill
No one is trained
So no one knows who will win or lose
Now the first group
Whoever wants to come, please step up
Who wants to compete with me?
I'm going
Me
Me with you?
Okay, go ahead
Go
When I see this, I feel like I can't do it
But today I came
I just want to
Do all the things I don't dare to do
Do them all once
I want to challenge
What I think I'm afraid of
Nini, go for it
Go for it
Okay, are the four of you ready?
Three, two, one
Put in more effort, higher, higher
Dai Yanni, you can do it
It's okay, very good.
I really felt like I couldn't do it.
I just couldn't move that dumbbell.
So this is my regret for today.
My dumbbell
bounced away.
Then I wanted to quickly go and straighten it.
And then throw it over again.
As I took a step,
the dumbbell
bounced back by itself.
I was speechless.
It came back and I threw it again.
I felt like after I threw it,
I rested there for
a minute.
Only then did I catch my breath.
I really think
it was quite exhausting.
So difficult.
This is too hard.
How can this be done?
Go, Chandlerpan, charge!
Okay.
Jinchao, go!
How embarrassing
I am so scared.
Are you ready?
Three, two, one
Go for it, Chandlerpan!
Chandlerpan
Finally figured out how to play at the end
Yes
But it's too late
That's definitely not a strength issue
It's like
How to control the rope
It flew
What's going on
Let's try again
Even a little force made it fly
It's really hard
This rope game
We athletes all do it
But we don't put dumbbells on it
What if no one can shake the dumbbell over the line
We are actually all skeptical
If you can't find the technique
you will be very, very tired
Three, two, one
Come on
Sun Rui, come on
Wang Yijin, come on
Push that dumbbell
Actually, you need to grasp a rhythm
and a feel
You could say that
And you also have to ensure
you don't throw it away
It will feel really difficult
After the second half
you realize you still need some strength
No matter how you swing it, it won't move
My dumbbell just stays there
Don't rush
Xi Ai, don't rush
Sister Xiai is exhausted.
Xiai has been too scared to go up.
Come on!
The main thing is to stay completely still.
What was the feeling in those last few seconds?
I really wanted it to cross the line.
But it just wouldn't move.
I felt helpless.
Look how amazing our Brother Yuan is.
When it was pushed to two-thirds,
I knew that spot
was a "dead end."
You have to use a lot of force to create a wave
to lift that dumbbell.
Let's go up in the next group.
Okay, sure.
Let's compete.
Alright, let's try.
We're both from the Northeast, both from Liaoning.
And we even sit together.
So we thought
we should go up and have a showdown.
Next group of contestants, please come up.
Get down, let's go.
This group includes Jiayuan and Li Xinyi
The champions of the previous two events are together
We need to congratulate the men's group champion, Li Xinyi
The champion of this event is Zhang Jiayuan
Four minutes thirty-four seconds sixty-one
Showdown
These two are the "kings" in my heart
Born with divine power
It's hard to tell between these two
Who can win
It's really hard to tell
Don't exert too much effort on this stretch
This stretch should
Even if you want to exert effort, you can't
A little bit
If you exert effort, it will fly
Yes
Three
Two
One
Don't rush, don't rush.
Okay.
Jiayuan is very fierce.
Zhang Jiayuan
Starting from scratch
There is a strong determination
Oh my God
That time, I almost
rolled over completely
It came off at one-fifth of the way
It's a pity, not as skilled as others, right
I really want to ask Zhang Jiayuan
Why did you look so smug when you came back
I don't want to
I'm managing my expressions
I don't know what expression to have
And then sometimes
After I do something that makes me really proud
I remain expressionless
It feels like I'm trying to look cool
But I'm not
I'm just really shocked
I was so shocked, my pupils were shaking
But only inside
You can check my expression then
Alright, next group
Did you sign up?
I don't want to go
You go, it's fine
It's actually easy to handle
There were too many samples before
Look at your arm
Now look at my arm
You used skill
Since we're here
That's what they say
Because when we were watching the first few,
whether you shake with both hands like this,
or shake with one hand like this,
there's actually a chance of it flipping over.
And also,
when you get to the middle and later stages,
once you stop,
it really becomes hard to move.
I say this time,
no matter what, participation is key.
That's what I believe.
Give it your all,
even if you can't reach that line,
even if you can't reach the finish line.
But I think,
if I don't even have the courage to challenge,
then,
I would really look down on myself.
Come on,
let's do this!
Yes, don't use too much force.
Technique.
Three, two, one
Go, Xikan
Xikan will be quick
So fast
Tired
Really tired
Beautiful
Extremely tired
"Playing dumb to catch the wise"
The main strategy is "playing dumb to catch the wise"
Just push it to the back
I was immediately shocked
I said, is it this fast?
He should be first, holding steady
He probably found some clever tricks in it
Because he observed several brothers before
When they were swinging the ropes
I might have been thinking about some techniques
Maybe this allowed me to "steal" it
I can go for the battle rope event
Bravely complete it
The goal I want to achieve
I was proud of myself at that moment
Next group
Their learning ability is very strong
They will continuously adjust
the rhythm of the rope
height
He uses skillful force, right
He just throws it on the ground, creating waves
Then it can be pushed over
Yes
The force is very gentle
Her force is very smooth
Didi is really quite impressive, Didi
So fast
Xiao Zhai, Xiao Zhai
Next group of contestants can come on stage now.
Where is Li Fei? Li Fei!
Let's go together, no one will be embarrassed.
You come, I go.
Come on, let's go.
Li Fei, you finally made your appearance, Li Fei.
Just watch how he embarrasses himself.
Reveal the punchline.
Three
Two
One
Li Fei
Don't rush, take it slow.
Wait a moment.
Yes.
Relax.
Keep it up.
Great job, great job.
Zhang Weiwei crossed the line, Zhang Weiwei
What is this?
Really beautiful, brother
They are almost the same
Yes
Starting point
Beautiful
Li Fei, fight for forty seconds
Returning to the starting point
I personally feel
Xu Mengjie still has a lot of potential
No, no
Don't give me hope
The greater the hope
the greater the disappointment
That won't happen, it's okay
We won't be disappointed
Alright, next
the last two from the boys' and girls' groups
Shall we go? Let's go
Let's go.
Take it off.
So heavy!
Get down a bit lower.
Three, two, one.
That girl is so fast.
She reached this point.
Isn't that too fast?
So fast.
How did she get past?
She got past in an instant.
Xu Mengjie, do you have ten seconds?
She made it.
I didn't even see it.
Just heard it start.
Come on
Get lower
Yes, come on
Down
Squat
Okay
Very good
Go for the last one
Here it comes
The last one
Okay
Passed
Not bad, not bad
Impressive
Great
Rainbow (Xu Mengjie) is really strong
Feels like she is
a born sports competitor
How can there be someone
who is good at every event
Really impressive
Don't you have ten seconds?
I do
No
Really?
You're so fast
I don't even know how it passed
That hurts more
Okay
Our results for this round
are now in Coach Lang's hands
We will only announce today's
top male and female
Do you want to guess before we announce?
Who do you think it will be?
I think the top male is Jiayuan
No
Xu Mengjie
Next, let's have Coach Lang
announce for us
Next
to announce the top
female athlete for this event
Xu Mengjie
Time: 6.34 seconds
Six seconds
So fast
Amazing
Too fast
Six seconds
Looking back now
It felt like it ended in just a couple of moves
Keep it up
That girl is so fast
So fast
I really enjoyed the process
I think so too
Because they actively encouraged me to participate
I did it
First place among the boys
Time: 11.60 seconds
Li Xikan
I
Never thought
Because my upper body strength is really weak
So I never thought
I could get first place in this event
Xikan is very fast
I've performed very well in the battle ropes
But I'm still a very ambitious person
I still hope to participate more
Following my own sportsmanship
Bravely accomplishing
the goals I want to achieve
Welcome back, everyone,
to the Gatorade "Supernova Sports Meet."
Welcome, everyone,
Stay hydrated and energized with Gatorade.
This program is brought to you by Gatorade,
which has specialized in electrolytes for 58 years.
as the title sponsor.
Thank you, Gatorade.
Okay
So in the five major projects
during the special assessments
everyone worked hard
and gave their all
showing their abilities
and the charm of sports
And now
the anticipated segment is about to begin
we will announce the rankings for everyone
Let's wait for just now
That project just now
Let's not look at the previous ones
Please look at the big screen
Li Quanzhe also took a long time
Look
He took quite a long time for each one
I'm fifth
You're fifth
Ouyang Didi
Look, I'm second
Just forty points behind
I'm in eighth place
Alright
They are too fierce, it's all them.
I am second to last.
Cao Enqi is very impressive.
You are sixth, right?
Our Gen1es girls are a bit intimidating.
They are so strong.
Twenty-three, right?
Our injuries were not in vain.
We are fourteen.
We, let's see.
Eighth.
Eighth place.
This year's Gatorade.
In the "Supernova Games".
All supernova athletes.
Will be divided into four teams.
In our live broadcast event.
Fight for the team.
So next.
First, we will announce.
The events in this year's live broadcast.
No archery this year?
Yes.
There is archery and team archery.
Street dance, team dance battle.
If it's a penalty kick, isn't that easy?
But if you have to hit exactly where you aim,
it's very difficult.
Next, everyone please
based on the physical test results,
choose four
who you think can
serve as team captains among the rookie athletes,
and write down their names.
The internal voting starts now.
I choose Chen Muchi
Chen Muchi seems quite fierce
Li Xinyi
You see, he fought really hard at that time
Because that was actually the hardest
Zhang Jiayuan, he was outstanding in the first project
Zando
He is great at dancing
The four candidates with the highest votes are
Ouyang Didi
Xu Mengjie
Li Xinyi
Zhang Jiayuan
Congratulations to the four of you
Actually, I still want to thank everyone
for recognizing me
and giving me great strength
which allowed me to become
the person with the priority choice
That girl is so fast
At that time, I
was very conflicted
Later, more people
wrote my name
At that moment, I thought I should give it a try
I never expected it at all
because I am one of the
younger girls here
and I didn't expect
the older brothers and sisters to trust me so much
and vote for me
so I feel that
I am grateful for their trust
Actually, I have thought about this question.
Because I indeed
performed quite well in those five competitions.
These four
have our priority team-up rights
will select team members in order
It should be noted that
the four athletes from "Peace Elite"
will join in the final round
because they must be reasonably distributed
one person per team
The four friends with priority selection rights
based on your recent vote counts
you are now ranked
In the first round
you
each team
can select
one person to join
Sister
You choose first
I'll choose
Alright, before the official registration begins,
a few more friends have been inspired by the dream
and are ready to join the adventure.
Who are they? Let's see.
Hello everyone, I am the actor Li Yunrui
Hello everyone, I am Liu Yu
Hello everyone, I am the singing and dancing artist, Oli.
Hello everyone, I am the actor Ren Hao
Hello everyone, I am Lù Zhuó
Ten diligent days, Li Gengyun
Ten diligent days, Old Six
Zhuo Yuan
Hello everyone, I am Wang Yiheng
I now recommend myself to everyone
My advantage in sports is that I have no disadvantages.
The sports I'm good at are basketball and football.
My physical coordination is still quite good.
The sport I'm good at is archery.
My advantage in sports is
long legs.
The sport I'm good at is flag football.
I like to try different sports in my daily life.
Basketball, cycling, archery, and so on.
My advantage is being versatile.
The sport I'm good at is table tennis.
The sports I'm good at are "Peace Elite" and basketball.
Various sports.
My advantage is being talented.
The sport I'm good at is
Anything except swimming.
The sport I'm best at is "Peace Elite."
In this "Supernova Games,"
the sports I most want to sign up for are
basketball and football.
archery,
flag football,
archery and "Peace Elite,"
high jump and "Peace Elite,"
basketball and street dance are both fine.
basketball, archery, and "Peace Elite."
I'm a landlubber.
As long as I don't have to swim,
I'm fine with anything.
The event I most want to sign up for is "Peace Elite."
Looking forward to meeting everyone on the field.
Let's win together once.
According to your vote counts,
you will choose team members in order.
I choose
This is ours
Really?
You want to choose him?
Betrayed me again
Why does everyone betray me
My friend
Tear it down, tear it down, tear it down
Looks good
Help me
Next
"Supernova Games" will enter
the team challenge
which includes the team obstacle challenge
and the basketball challenge
Go for it
Go Li Daben
Zando is so fast
He's especially fast
Wu Zhengrong
Go for it
"Special Forces"
Well done, keep it up
Go for it
Sun Rui is so fierce
YZZ (Ye Zhiwei) is so fast
So fast
Go Li Daben!
Li Daben is handsome.
Go Sun Yue!
So handsome.
Iconic moment from "Supernova Games."
Coach Sun's three-pointer went in immediately.
So impressive.
Go for it!
Good.
Dan Jingyao, watch your face
Be careful
It's all water up here
Oh my god
It's difficult
My heart is racing
It's okay
He must be really nervous
Our team is falling behind
I knew this wasn't over
But I really want to win
We have to give it our all
Our goal is to be the champions
I need to catch my breath
Sun Yue, pull her
Our team must win
Hold tight
Step firmly
One, two, three
Come on
Hurry
Qiao Yiyu
Come on
It's so hard, I want to cry
Beautiful
Amazing
Victory is assured.